what were functional modifiers in this
该视频中的功能修改器是什么，我将解释什么
video I'm going to explain what
functional modifiers I show you how to
功能修饰符我向您展示如何编写功能修饰符并解释原因
write function modifier and explain why
they are useful function modifiers are
它们是有用的函数修饰符，是可重用的代码，可以附加到
reusable code that can be attached to a
function this reusable code can be
可以在代码之前和/或之后执行此可重用代码的功能
executed before and/or after the
function is executed
功能执行
we'll go over the examples in remix in
在第一个示例中，我们将讨论混音中的示例。
the first example we'll go over the
basic syntax for writing a function
编写函数修饰符的基本语法，我们将创建一个函数
modifier and we'll create a function
modifier to restrict write access to a
修饰符以限制对第二个示例的函数的写访问
function in the second example I'll go
over the syntax for passing parameters
传递参数到函数修饰符中的语法，我们将
into a function modifier and we'll
create a function modifier for input
在这一点上，为输入验证创建一个函数修饰符，我还将
validation at this point I'll also
explain why a function modifier is
解释为什么函数修饰符对第三个示例有用
useful for the third example I'll
quickly explain what a reaction C hat is
快速解释一下什么是C hat是什么反应，我们将编写一个函数修饰符来
and we'll write a function modifier to
prevent this hack here we have a
在这里防止这种黑客入侵，我们有合同
contract
when this contract is deployed is sets
部署此合同时，将所有者变量设置为在发件人上发送消息
the owner variable to messaged on sender
message the sender is the sender of the
消息发件人是交易的发件人，因此在这种情况下
transaction so in this case it will be
the sender of this transaction that
在合同内部署了该合同的交易的发送者
deployed this contract inside a contract
we have a function called change owner
我们有一个叫做变更拥有者的功能变更拥有者接收了
change owner takes in the address of the
new owner as input inside this function
新所有者作为此函数内部的输入，它首先调用该函数的唯一所有者
it first calls the function only owner
the function only owner checks that
该功能仅所有者检查该消息，即发件人等于
message that sender is equal to the
current owner if it is not equal to the
当前所有者，如果它不等于当前所有者，则此函数
current owner then this function
thousand-aire and the transaction fails
千人游戏，然后交易失败，功能有效地址检查
next the function valid address checks
that the new owner is not equal to the 0
如果新所有者等于0地址，则新所有者不等于0地址
address if it is equal to the 0 address
again this function throws an error and
再次，此函数引发错误，并且一旦两个交易失败
the transaction fails once the two
functions execute without any errors the
函数执行没有任何错误，当前所有者已设置为新所有者
current owner is set to the new owner
let's go over how we will use function
让我们研究一下如何使用函数修饰符来限制仅写访问
modifiers to restrict write access only
to the current owner and how we use a
当前所有者，以及我们如何使用功能修饰符来验证
function modifier to validate the
address of the new owner first we'll
首先，将新功能所有者的地址转换为新所有者的地址
turn the function only owner into a
function modifier so replace the keyword
函数修饰符，因此将关键字函数替换为关键字修饰符，然后
function with the keyword modifier and
remove the keyword public
删除关键字public
we won't need
我们将不需要修改用于检查
modify the code that checks that the
sender of the transaction is equal to
交易的发送者等于所有者，因此我们不会修改此部分
the owner so we won't modify this part
of the code on the next time type
下一次的代码的类型是下划线，然后是分号
underscore and followed by a semicolon
the underscore is a special character
下划线是一个特殊字符，您只能在内部使用
that you can only use inside the
function modifier and it tells ability
函数修饰符，它告诉您执行其余代码的能力，因此一旦执行
to execute the rest of the code so once
this modifier is attached to the
此修饰符附加到功能更改所有者此下划线
function change owner this underscore
would tell solidity to execute code
会告诉我们在函数内执行代码的坚固性，您可以附加一个
inside the function and you can attach a
function modifier to a function by
通过在函数中声明修饰符来对函数进行修饰
declaring the modifier in the function
signature
签名
and go ahead and delete the function
并继续删除该函数的唯一所有者，因为我们将其重写为
only owner since we rewrote it as a
function modifier
函数修饰符接下来让我们看一下如何传递
next let's go over how to pass
parameters into a function modifier
参数放入函数修饰符中，首先将关键字函数替换为
first replace the keyword function with
the keyword modifier and also remove the
关键字修饰符，并删除关键字public
keyword public
we won't need to change
我们不需要在下一行更改输入验证
for input validation on the next line
type underscore followed by a semicolon
键入下划线，后跟一个分号，所以在这里，我们再次要说的是
so here again we're telling solidity to
execute the rest of the code and we can
执行其余代码，我们可以通过以下方式附加功能修饰符
attach the function modifier by
declaring it in the function signature
在函数签名中声明它，您可以将参数传递给
and you can pass parameters into a
function modifier the same way that you
函数修饰符，就像您在函数中继续前进一样
would in a function finally go ahead and
delete the function valid address since
删除函数有效地址，因为我们已将该函数转换为函数
we turned that function into a function
modifier function modifiers can make
修饰符函数修饰符可以使您的代码更具可读性，这是
your code more readable here is the
function change owner before we use the
函数更改所有者，然后在函数内部使用函数修饰符
function modifier inside the function we
do some validations before we update the
在将所有者更新为新所有者之前进行一些验证，然后移动
owner to the new owner we move the
validation that was done inside the
在函数内部完成的验证到函数签名中
function into the function signature
using the function modifier we made our
使用功能修饰符，我们明确了谁可以调用它的意图
intent clear on who can call this
function and what kind of inputs are
函数以及该函数允许什么样的输入
allowed into this function
so now let's cover the third example
现在让我们介绍第三个示例可重入的海纳格（Sea Hag），让我们看看
reentrant Sea Hag and let's see how a
function modifier can prevent this
函数修饰符可以防止这种攻击，首先让我们谈谈
attack first let's talk about what a
reaction C hat is imagine there are two
反应C帽子想象有两个合同a和一个合同a
contracts contract a and contract be a
function f inside contract a is called
合同a内部的函数f在调用a的函数内部被调用
inside the function that calls a
function inside contract B and contract
合约B和合约B内部的函数导致返回到函数f
B cause back into the function f the
function f inside contract a starts
合同a中的函数f在上一个合同之前开始执行其代码
executing its code before the previous
call to the function completes it calls
对该函数的调用完成后，它将再次调用函数G和合同B，并且
function G and contract B again and
function G calls back into function f
函数G回调到函数f，这可以无限期地继续使用
and this can continue indefinitely using
the sack millions of dollars were stolen
在未来的视频中，数百万美元的麻袋被盗了，我将在
in the future video I'll go over this in
more details so how can we prevent this
更多细节，以便我们如何防止这种情况的发生，我们可以防止这种情况的发生
from happening we can guard against this
act by preventing a function to be
通过阻止函数在其首先执行时被调用来执行操作
called while it is still executing first
let's see an example of a function that
我们来看一个可以在静止状态下调用的函数的示例
can be called while it is still
executing here we have a function called
在这里执行，我们有一个称为减量的函数，该注释取一个整数
decrement that comment takes an integer
valuable named I and it documents the
有价值的名为I的文件，如果I仍在，它通过I记录状态变量X
state variable X by I if I is still
greater than 1 it calls back into itself
大于1时，它会以I减1回调回自身，所以让我们看看会发生什么
with I minus 1 so let's see what happens
with the function decrement when we pass
当我们传入3作为输入时函数递减
in 3 as input
on the top you see the current value of
在顶部，您可以看到状态变量X的当前值为10。
the state variable X which is 10 on the
right you'll see a stack of functions
正确，您会看到一堆被调用但尚未完成的函数
that are called and have not finished
executing it decrements the state
执行它会将状态变量X减3，所以现在X的值是
variable X by 3 so now the value of X is
7 since 3 is greater than 1 we call
7因为3大于1，所以我们用3减1再次调用文档，所以
document again with 3 minus 1 so the
function document with the input 2 is
输入为2的功能文档称为递减状态变量
called it decrements the state variable
X by 2 and since 2 is greater than 1 we
X乘2，由于2大于1，我们称文档为2减1
call document with 2 minus 1
we again decrement the state variable X
我们再次将状态变量X减1，所以现在X的客户值是
by 1 so now the client value of X is
equal to 4 since 1 is not greater than 1
等于4，因为1不大于1不会调用文档并递减
document is not called and decrement
want finished executing so we'll remove
要完成执行，因此我们将其从函数调用堆栈中删除
it from the stack of function calls
now decrement twos execution is also
现在减法二的执行也完成了，因此我们也将其从
finished so we also remove it from the
stack of function calls and finally
函数调用堆栈，最后文档3完成了执行，我们
document 3 finished its execution and we
are left to state variable x equals 4
留给状态变量x等于4，所以现在让我们看看如果我们
so now let's see what would happen if we
had a function modifier that prevented
具有防止递归调用的函数修饰符，我们将创建一个
recursive calls we will create a
modifier called Nouri entrance e inside
在修饰符内称为Nouri入口e的修饰符，我们首先检查了
the modifier we first checked that the
boolean variable lock is set to false
布尔变量lock设置为false接下来，我们将其设置为true，然后调用
next we set it to true and then call the
function and then after the function we
函数，然后在函数之后将其设置回false
set it back to false
finally we attach this modifier
最后，我们将此修饰符附加到功能文档中，让我们来看一下
to the function document let's go over
how this modifier would prevent a
该修饰符如何防止递归调用
recursive call
first the state barrier bollocked is set
首先，在功能文档为
to false when the function document is
called it first sets the law to true and
调用它首先将定律设置为true，然后开始执行其代码，
it starts executing its code and it
calls itself again with three minus one
再次用三减一来调用自己，但现在由于阁楼等于二，所以
but now since loft is equal to two the
required statement fails and the
此视频中的必填语句失败，交易失败，我们
transaction fails in this video we
talked about functional modifiers
谈到功能修饰符功能修饰符是可重用的代码
function modifiers are reusable code
that can be run before and/or after a
可以在功能的一些常见用例之前和/或之后运行
function some common use cases of
function modifiers are to restrict write
函数修饰符用于限制输入验证和输入的写访问权限
access for an input validation and for
reentrant seagard
未来影片中的可重入的Seagard，我们将重新审视v
in a future video we'll revisit the v
entrance e act in more details so stay
请更详细地了解我们的表演，敬请关注，非常感谢您的观看和
tuned thank you so much for watching and
I'll see you soon
一会儿见